Inventory of the Ferdinand Peroutka papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Radio Free Europe Broadcast Sound Recordings, 1955-1956, undated
  - Fragment of an interview with Peroutka, in Czech, undated (Reel 37)
    On Peroutka's political career after 1945, his decision to emigrate from Czechoslovakia in 1948, Vladimír Clementis and George Orwell
  - Fragment of an interview with Peroutka, in Czech, undated (Reel 38)
    Use copy reference number: 84052_a_0003689
    On George Orwell and the Czechoslovak exile culture
  - Fragment of an interview with Peroutka, in Czech, undated (Reel 39)
    Use copy reference number: 84052_a_0003690
    On Peroutka's decision to emigrate from Czechoslovakia in 1948
  - Funeral service for Peroutka, Part 1, in Czech and English, 1978 (Reel 40)
    Use copy reference number: 84052_a_0003561
    Commendation by a priest and speeches of Josef Škvorecký and Jiří Voskovec
  - Funeral service for Peroutka, Part 2, in Czech, 1978 (Reel 41)
    Use copy reference number: 84052_a_0003562
    Speech by Karel Steinbach and the Czechoslovak anthem